horse-games.org 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy

Horse-Games.org Privacy Policy

This privacy statement is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our web site. It will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices, and the needs of our visitors.

This statement covers the following topics:  
Information Collected and How it is Used  
Personal Information and Choice  
Public Access to Information  
Security  
Disclaimer  
E-Mail Privacy Warning  
Contact Information

When you browse our Web site, you do so without revealing your identity. Personal information, including your E-mail address, is not collected without your knowledge. The use of and access to your personal information is restricted to those employees who need to know that information to provide services or support to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.

Horse-Games.org does not plan to divulge personal information collected or information disclosed voluntarily, but we may be required to do so pursuant to State or Federal law. If you believe that your personal information is being used for a purpose other than that which was intended when submitted, please contact us at info@horse-games.org

You may choose whether to provide personal information online. "Personal Information" is information about a natural person that identifies a specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual's name, email address, and account password. A domain name or Internet protocol address is not considered personal information.

We do not collect personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You may choose not to provide personal information online. Your choice not to participate in this activity will not impair your ability to browse this Web site and read or view any information posted on this site.

E-Mail Privacy Warning  
E-mail is not a secure communication's medium. Personal information sent via the Internet can be intercepted. You may, therefore, wish to reconsider the advisability of sending messages that contain highly sensitive or personal information to this Internet address.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
Horse-Games.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense,

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.horse-games.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.horse-games.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.horse-games.oeg's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Important notice to all game developers:  
Almost all game hosted on our site are copyrighted by their respective owner . If you are owner to some of games and you won't it appear to our site just write an e-mail with your request and we will remove these games immediately .

Important notice to all photographers :  
If anyone of you think that some picture published in horse-games.org (pictures of Jigsaws Puzzles etc.) is your property , and you won't appear in our site simply send us an e-mail at info@horse-games.org and we will remove that picture (game) within 24 hours . Horse-Games.org neither sold nor published pictures in high resolution and therefore they are not available to download from horse-games.org . All of the pictures which are in high resolution (higher than 800x600 pixels) are property of horse-games.org
